The potion that cures all diseases?
With this potion.
perhaps it could cure
my mother's Eternal Slumber.
Creating Elixir of Life
requires three items.
I don't have any of them yet.
but I know where to find them.
However...
With my current strength. entering
that gate would be committing suicide.
I must level up even higher.
I must...
become stronger.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Eh. you decided to accept it?
The situation is different now.
For your proposal
for 19 C-rank raid missions. I'm in.
That's great.
But I have one condition.
Just say it.
Just you and me.
The two of us.
Just the two of us
to conquer C-rank dungeons?
That's right.
But... To enter the C-rank gate.
we need at least eight people. don't we?
Just find people to make up the numbers.
like what Hwang Dongsuk did.
But...
Will it be dangerous?
It depends on how you see it.
As long as the two of us are safe.
we can complete the 19 raid missions
without anyone getting hurt.
A team unscathed
in 19 consecutive missions.
Isn't that a perfect way
to make your father acknowledge you?
I see.
Let's do it. Jinwoo.
I'll take care
of team members and the gate.
Come out.
What do you want?
Truly surprising.
No wonder you're an S-rank hunter.
I couldn't find the right moment
to speak to you.
Sorry for disturbing you
during your training.
Here is my business card.
It's been over a decade
since the gates appeared.
The world has changed drastically.
Now infrastructure. economy.
media. and even politics
are all inextricably linked
to the dungeon.
Especially the infrastructure
that is vital to the common people.
Without resources from the dungeon.
it'd be hard to sustain operations.
And the only ones who can bring
such valuable resources back
are the hunters.
And the one managing these hunters
is the government agency
known as Hunter's Association.
The Hunter's Association
will classify awakened hunters.
register and manage them accordingly.
They assign manpower
to deal with unwanted gates
and also bear the heavy
responsibility in Dungeon Breaks.
But in the end. the association
is just a government agency.
These resources are enough
to sustain operations.
but those who control
most of resources are guilds.
the corporations
that center around hunters.
The guilds obtain massive profits
from the resources
acquired from the dungeons.
Among them. Hunters Guild.
White Tiger Guild.
Feind Guild. Fame Guild. and Knights Guild
are the five major guilds in the country.
These guilds have almost
monopolized all the resources.
I cannot just sit here and watch.
Not to mention letting
these resources vital to the people
fall into the hands of those brutes.
It should be us. who have supported
the nation's development.
to take on the responsibility
to manage them.
For this purpose.
we must establish a guild.
Yes.
That being said.
as my brother and I jointly run a guild
and headhunt S-rank hunters.
the risks are too great.
But.
my current self...
It stopped counting the quests
that exceeded the goal?
Does it mean I can't get the reward
for the previous secret quest.
Cursed Random Loot Box?
I thought I could get another item
like The Demon Castle's Key.
No.
Even if it's a regular random box.
it's possible to get something
like an instance dungeon's key.
Makes sense.
At this level. three ability points
are no longer enough.
I really want to level up quickly.
but now I can only wait
for Jinho's C-rank dungeon missions.
That's right.
Penalty Zone.
As long as I kill those centipedes there...
No.
Now I might escape
more easily than before.
But to defeat it...
Besides. I might not be able
to gain any points.
D-rank gate mission?
It's a request from the
Hunter's Association for making up a team.
which means I can't fight alone.
Should I refuse?
Well. it's better than nothing.
I have no time to waste.
I still can't defeat you. master.
It won't be so easy for you to defeat me.
However. it's still a pity.
I really want to spar with you
in your top condition.
You're bringing this up again.
It's been several months.
An urgent call-up?
Low-rank hunters are
just fated to run errands.
Master. have you never
thought about retiring?
Retiring?
Indeed.
An old man with only one arm
might only be a hindrance.
No. that's not what I meant...
I lost an arm. yet I survived.
I don't have much time left.
At least before I die.
I hope to do more for this world.
I got a new raid mission.
Dear.
Isn't it about time
you give up being a hunter?
You bring it up again?
Because it's too dangerous.
So many people died in the last mission.
You almost didn't make it out. right?
Hmm... Yeah.
Daddy. hug.
But. next year.
Eunji will be going to kindergarten.
and Eunha is also going to junior high.
We need money. don't we?
That's true.
It's okay.
The association wouldn't send us low-rank
hunters to overly dangerous dungeons.
Last time was just an exception.
Yes.
Sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
Don't mind it.
Be careful. okay?
Okay.
I love you.
Daddy.
Oh. what is it?
Daddy. are you very powerful?
Of course.
I can defeat scary monsters.
That's amazing.
Daddy. you really are the best.
You tricked me.
What are you referring to?
You pushed the bothersome
media interview onto me.
I saw it on TV.
You did super well.
Your speech really hit home.
Stop saying that.
That was originally your job. right?
But Chairman Go requested
to show the public the work attitude
and honest character of strong hunters.
I don't think
I'm quite suited for this task.
So you know you're not honest.
Forget it.
All right. what do you want from me?
You didn't summon me
just to hear me complain. right?
I must inform you of a recent event.
Yoojin Construction
seems to want to establish a guild.
I know that. They are looking
for people under the table.
I've also heard
they are poaching my people.
Since you have known it.
it seems I am meddling unnecessarily.
You knew all along that I would know.
Stop beating around the bush.
I'll ask you again.
What do you want from me?
You haven't been calling recently.
Is everything going well?
-Hmm.
-How's your work?
Hmm.
It's okay.
You have always been timid.
Doesn't working as a Hunter
make you uncomfortable?
I heard you're a B-rank hunter.
If it were someone else.
they would probably be strong.
But you'd probably be a burden to others.
You'd better come back
and help out at home.
Your dad is also worried about you...
Don't make decisions for me. okay?
I'll make my own decisions.
I don't need you to interfere.
Wait. why are you...
A burden to others?
But.
I'll just give it another go.
Excuse me.
What is it. Hunter Cha Hae-In?
Someone from Yoojin Construction
tried to poach me during my training.
I came to report to you.
I see.
It seems they want
to establish a new guild
and want me to be the guild master.
You've come to report to me.
Can I take it as
you've declined their offer?
Yes. I declined right on the spot.
I'm relieved.
Thank you very much.
It's nothing.
By the way.
I saw Mr. Baek on my way here.
What did he come to talk to you about?
What are your thoughts on Jeju Island?
Jeju Island?
Why do you ask that?
After the third raid mission.
the island was ordered off-limits.
Now. there are only periodic
patrols along the coast.
And the public is informed that
a memorial service is held there annually.
People have forgotten the island
along with the fear.
But that's unavoidable. isn't it?
However.
whether the gates
have become part of daily life.
or I'm hailed
as the ultimate weapon of mankind.
I will not forget that island.
nor what happened there.
In the near future.
I will definitely conquer
that island again.
For that reason.
we cannot afford to be divided now.
We must unite. increase our numbers.
and sway public opinion.
That's what those interviews
and nurturing of newcomers are for?
Aren't you the same?
You have also left something behind
on that island.
Eunseok.
Byung-gu.
Please.
Help me...
kill them.
I'm going out.
Still working on the holiday?
You've been doing this often lately.
Yes.
You used to get hurt
every time you went through the gate.
Is this the result of exercise?
Perhaps.
Anyway. I can earn money steadily now.
Isn't that a good thing?
It is...
Eh. brother? Don't you need luggage?
No need. I'm heading out.
Eh. wait.
It's not like going
to the convenience store.
My awakening is not
a physical type of awakening.
My swordsmanship
can't harm the magic beasts.
The swordsmanship
that I've practiced for decades
turns out to be useless in the dungeon.
The fact that I. a swordsman. awakened
as a Mage is also a twist of fate.
Could there be some reason behind it?
You are...
Mr. Song.
I was wondering if I was mistaken.
Are you Sung?
Long time no see.
I never thought that
I would see you here again.
That being said.
where is that immature young man?
In just a few months.
you've changed so much.
And...
How come your leg is fine?
Well... When I woke up in the hospital.
my leg was back to normal.
I see.
There might be a high-level healer among
the hunters who came to rescue.
Regardless.
it's great to see a young talent
making a recovery.
Thank you.
But you...
As for me.
I didn't get it treated soon enough.
But it's all right.
What's more important is.
I heard from the association staff
that you are all right.
but I'm glad to be able
to see you like this again.
Mr. Song. why did you come here?
I was summoned by the association.
I heard that it's a D-rank mission.
You are in it too?
I can't believe this.
The members from that mission.
Jinwoo.
Joohee.
And
Mr. Kim and Mr. Kang.
So be it.
After all. we abandoned Sung
and fled that place.
Kim even drew his sword against me.
I suppose he is too ashamed to face us.
But...
The five survivors of that tragedy
are once again together.
So...
Jinwoo.
It's you. right?
You've changed a lot.
Yes. It's been a long time.
You've grown much taller.
And your leg.
When I came to visit. you were already...
Visit?
Oh.
There's a beautiful lady here too.
What's the matter?
Are you with that young man?
Why don't you come to us...
Shut up.
You are not here for a hike.
Now. I will explain
to all the general hunters.
Please come this way.
What's going on?
They are the substitute prisoners
who will join you on the mission today.
Substitute prisoners?
We have to go on a mission with criminals?
Although they are hunters
with convictions.
they wish to lessen their sentences.
so they will not harm you.
There is a shortage
of manpower in this area.
Please bear with us.
How can this be?
Kang Taeshik from Hunter's Association's
Surveillance Team will accompany you.
He is a B-rank hunter.
Even in the event of danger. he can
easily deal with three C-rank prisoners.
So please rest assured.
Something feels wrong.
Joohee. you shouldn't go.
What about you?
I'm going.
Then I'm going too.
I understand.
Ah. the taste of freedom is wonderful.
We are not slaves.
Do you have to treat us this way?
Shut up.
You are prisoners.
If you dare to make a reckless move.
you know what will happen to you.
I'm Kang Taeshik from the Hunter's
Association's Surveillance Team.
I will take responsibility
for monitoring them.
Please be assured.
Who will be the leader
of this raid mission?
Sung. can I be the Captain?
Yes. of course.
Thank you for giving me another chance.
Mr. Song.
That day. due to my mistake.
seven people lost their lives.
I am to blame
for not being able to protect them.
But. thanks to you. six people survived.
Please allow me to thank you
on behalf of the five of them.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Mr. Song. Please raise your head.
Kim. are you okay with me
being the Captain?
Whatever.
That's it then.
I'll lead the team in the dungeon.
Understood.
Then let's set off.
So. let's go
into the dungeon.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today